techwoo.com 2017-12-20

# BuxUp | Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

BuxUp Limited (“ **we** “, “ **us** “) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy (together with our terms of website use) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 ( **“the 1998 Act”** ), the data controller is BuxUp Limited, (a company registered in England and Wales with a company registration number: 05974418) whose address is 401 Marshall Building, 3 Hermitage Street, London W2 1PB UK.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION**

We can collect and process the following data about you:

\- Information that you provide by filling in forms on our website www.buxup.com ( **“Our Website”** ). This includes information provided at the time of registering to use Our Website, subscribing to our service, our newsletter, posting material or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with Our Website;

\- Information the you provide to us when you contact us. We may make and keep a record of the information you share with us;

\- Information that you provide to us by completing surveys or participating in competitions. We may ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them;

\- Details of transactions you carry out through Our Website or otherwise with us and of the fulfilment of your orders with third parties concluded through Our Website or otherwise; and

\- Details of your visits to Our Website including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.

**COOKIES** **AND IP ADDRESSES**

We can collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration to report aggregate information to our advertisers and/or affiliates. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

Please note that our advertisers and/or affiliates may also use cookies, over which we have no control. If you visit a third party website using a link on Our Website, that third party site may use cookies.

The Privacy Policy of any third party website operator will apply to your visits to any third party websites (including those accessed via a link on Our Website).

Cookies are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site.

**STORING PERSONAL DATA**

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

All information you provide to us via email or Our Website is stored on our secure servers or the secure servers of third parties authorised by us.

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of Our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to Our Website; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

**USE OF THE INFORMATION**

We use information held about you in the following ways:

\- To ensure that content from Our Website is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;

\- To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes;

\- To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us;

\- To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;

\- To notify you about changes to Our Website, goods and/or services; and

\- We may also use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these. If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you via Our Website. We will not otherwise contact you by electronic means to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you, unless you have consented to this. If you are a new customer, and where we permit selected third parties to use your data, we (or they) will only contact you by electronic means to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you if you have consented to this.

If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data;

We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers, but we may provide them with aggregate information about our users (for example, we may inform them that 50 men aged under 40 have clicked on their advertisement on any given day). We may also use such aggregate information to help advertisers reach the kind of audience they want to target (for example, men in W1). We may make use of the personal data we have collected from you to enable us to comply with our advertisers’ wishes by displaying their advertisement to that target audience.

**DISCLOSURE OF THE INFORMATION**

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.

We may also use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these by post, email or telephone.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

\- In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.

\- If we or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.

\- If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Website Terms of Use and/or other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of us, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and prevention, credit risk reduction and to pursue debtors.

\- If we use a third party to host the servers on which your personal information is stored.

\- In any other manner mentioned elsewhere in this policy.

**YOUR RIGHTS**

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes, or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at info(at)buxup.com.

Our Website may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our customers, registered members, suppliers, partner networks, advertisers, affiliates and other third parties. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies or the content or operation of these websites. Please check these policies and the terms of the websites before you submit any personal data to these websites.

**ACCESS TO INFORMATION**

The 1998 Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with The 1998 Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

We want to make sure that your personal data is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate.

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.

**CONTACT**

If you have questions, comments and requests regarding our privacy policy, please do not hesitate to contact us at info(at)buxup.com.

Last Updated 12.01.2017
